---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&category=9&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 05:33:54 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=41820df934176b277dcf2480bb2fe650; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        company did Valve cooperate with in the creation of the Vive?","correct_answer":"HTC","incorrect_answers":["Oculus","Google","Razer"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In past times,
        what would a gentleman keep in his fob pocket?","correct_answer":"Watch","incorrect_answers":["Money","Keys","Notebook"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the name
        of the Jewish New Year?","correct_answer":"Rosh Hashanah","incorrect_answers":["Elul","New
        Year","Succoss"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Nutella
        is produced by the German company Ferrero.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How many colors
        are there in a rainbow?","correct_answer":"7","incorrect_answers":["8","9","10"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which American-owned
        brewery led the country in sales by volume in 2015?","correct_answer":"D.
        G. Yuengling and Son, Inc","incorrect_answers":["Anheuser Busch","Boston Beer
        Company","Miller Coors"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        country, not including Japan, has the most people of japanese decent?","correct_answer":"Brazil","incorrect_answers":["China","South
        Korea","United States of America"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The
        Canadian $1 coin is colloquially known as a what?","correct_answer":"Loonie","incorrect_answers":["Boolie","Foolie","Moodie"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of the
        following is not an Ivy League University?","correct_answer":"Stanford","incorrect_answers":["University
        of Pennsylvania","Harvard","Princeton"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The
        &ldquo;fairy&rdquo; type made it&rsquo;s debut in which generation of the
        Pokemon core series games?","correct_answer":"6th","incorrect_answers":["2nd","7th","4th"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 05:33:54 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
